Director: OK. Be quiet, please.
Scene one, take one.
Lights, camera... action!
Daisy: Hello, Sam.
Sam: Hello, Daisy.
Daisy: Come in. Sit down.
We need to talk.
Sam: Talk? What about?
Daisy: Us. You and me.
Sam: Listen to me, Daisy. I love you!
Do you love me?
Daisy: I don’t know, Sam. I need time.
Sam: And Paul?
Do you love him?
Daisy: Don’t talk about Paul.
Yes, I like Paul, but I don’t love him.
You don’t understand.
Sam: Don’t cry, Daisy. Please don’t cry.
Director: Cut! Great! I like it.
Director: OK. Scene two.
This is a big scene, Daisy, go to the windows.
Open them.
Sam, go to Daisy, stand next to her.
Daisy, look at him. That’s great. Don’t move.
Sam: What do I say to her? I don’t remember.
Director: Nothing.
Don’t say anything. Just take her hands and look into her eyes.
That’s it! Cut!